(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
2023/01/02
2023/07/25
4th anniversary
白銀ノエル4周年記念 Summer Vacances
Shirogane Noel 4th Anniversary Summer Vacances
もうハイになっちゃえよねオッケー
Just get high already, okay?
受け取ってよねオッケー
Accept it, okay?
君のことが好きだもん
Because I like you!
はっぴー
作詞・作曲: DECO*27
Happy
Lyrics/Composition: DECO*27
いい感じって勘違いしちゃって
I'm misunderstanding that things are going well
恥ずかしくなっちゃうじゃん バカバカ
And I'm getting embarrassed, dummy dummy!
あ、待ってそれ以上 私に近づかないで後生後生
Ah, wait, don't come any closer than that, please, please!
押し込んだ感情が脱走脱走
My suppressed feelings are escaping, escaping!
想いのドミノ 倒してみて
Try knocking over the dominoes of my thoughts
止まらなくて困るかも
They might not stop, and I might be in trouble
言いたいこと全部言っちゃう魔法
A magic that says everything I want to say
蕩けちゃうくらいの砂糖
Enough sugar to make me melt
たっぷりかけて
Pour it on thick
それでハッピーじゃん 君が笑いなら
Then it's happy, if you're laughing
それがハッピーじゃん 心キスしてジャンプして
That's happy, kiss my heart and jump
落ち込んでダメダメだって一回の君の笑顔で
Even if I'm down and everything's no good, with just one of your smiles
全部忘れちゃうから
I'll forget everything!
もう何をやったってはいオッケー
No matter what I did, yes, okay!
謝ったらはいオッケー
If I apologize, yes, okay!
甘えすぎたら目瞑っといてね
If I'm being too spoiled, keep your eyes closed, okay?
もうハイになっちゃえよねオッケー
Just get high already, okay?
受け取ってよねオッケー
Accept it, okay?
君のことが好きだもん
Because I like you!
伝えたい言葉が溢れ出す気持ちが君を目指して
The words I want to say, the feelings overflowing, they aim for you
また大渋滞して
And cause another traffic jam
鳴り響くクラクション 思い切っちゃえば楽勝
Horns honking; if I just go for it, it'll be a breeze
踏んでしまうのはいつもブレーキなんだよ
But what I end up stepping on is always the brake
想いのオセロ 返してみて
Try turning over the Othello pieces of my thoughts
挟まれたら染まるまで
Until they're trapped and dyed completely
...かもう
...already.
言いたいこと全部言えちゃう魔法で
With magic that lets me say everything I want to say,
とろけちゃうくらいの砂糖で
with enough sugar to make me melt,
ドキドキさせたい
I want to make your heart race.
でもはっぴーじゃん 見てくれなくちゃ
But it's Happy-Jan, you've gotta watch me.
また はっぴーじゃん 心フリークして
Again, Happy-Jan, my heart is freaking out,
ショートして
short-circuiting.
落ち込んでダメダメだって 一回の君の笑顔で
Even when I'm down and out, just one of your smiles
全部忘れちゃうけど
makes me forget it all.
それもはっぴーじゃん 君といられたら
That's also Happy-Jan, if I can be with you.
つまり はっぴーじゃん 心キスして
In short, Happy-Jan, kiss my heart,
ジャンプして
and jump.
落ち込んでダメダメだって 一回の君の笑顔で
Even when I'm down and out, just one of your smiles
全部忘れちゃうから
makes me forget it all.
もう何をやったってはい、OK!
No matter what I do, yes, OK!
謝ったらはい、OK!
If I apologize, yes, OK!
甘えすぎたら愛でといてね
If I'm too clingy, please just love me.
もうハイになったらはい、OK!
When I'm feeling high, yes, OK!
受け取ってねはい、OK!
Please accept it, yes, OK!
君のことが好きなんだよ
I really love you.
もう何があったってはい、OK!
No matter what happens, yes, OK!
泣いちゃってもはい、OK!
Even if I cry, yes, OK!
大好きのハグきっと続く
Hugs full of love will surely continue.
もうハイになったらはい、OK!
When I'm feeling high, yes, OK!
受け取ってねはい、OK!
Please accept it, yes, OK!
君のことが好き好き好き好きすぎて
Because I love-love-love-love you so much,
私ハッピーだもん
I'm just so happy.
はーい！はい！うわー、夏が来たー！
Yay! Yes! Wow, summer is here!
ということで、皆さん、こんまっする！
And with that, hello everyone, Konmuscle!
ホロライブ3期生の、脳筋女騎士こと、白銀ノエルです！
I'm Shirogane Noel, the muscle-brained female knight from Hololive 3rd Generation!
今日は団長の4周年ということで、ライブに来てくださりありがとうございます！
Today marks my 4th anniversary, so thank you all for coming to the live!
こちらにね、ハッシュタグ「白銀ノエル4周年」とありますので、
Over here we have the hashtag #ShiroganeNoel4thAnniversary,
もしよければTwitterにて、スクショとかね、感想とかね、
so if you'd like, please post lots of screenshots and your thoughts on Twitter!
いっぱい呟いてくれると嬉しいです！お願いします！
It would make me really happy! Please do!
いやしかもね、なんと今年の、サマーの水着もね、
And what's more, I'm already wearing
早速着ちゃっております！可愛いでしょー？
this year's summer swimsuit! Isn't it cute?
いやめちゃめちゃ可愛いんでね、ちょっと団長だけでもね、
It's super cute, and while I'm sure you're all happy just seeing me,
みんなすごい嬉しいと思うけど、ちょっとゲストさんとかとね、
I'm thinking of singing and dancing
一緒にこのサマーの水着で歌ったり踊ったりとかもしちゃおうかなーと思うので、
in this summer swimsuit with some guests as well.
じゃあ早速いっちゃいますか！
So, shall we get right to it?
もしよければね、最後まで見てってくれると嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
I hope you enjoy it until the very end! Thank you!
では、歌うぞー！うー！
Now then, let's sing! Woo!
お願いマッスル
Please Muscle
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたい
Please muscle, I want to be super popular.
お願いマッスル めっちゃ痩せたい、イェス！
Please muscle, I want to lose lots of weight, yes!
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたいから
Please muscle, because I want to be super popular...
ウー！ (キレてるよ！) ハー！ (キレてるよ！)
Woo! (You're ripped!) Ha! (You're ripped!)
筋肉にお願い！
I'm counting on my muscles!
ヒップレイズ！ サイドベント！ 腹筋6LDKかい！
Hip Raise! Side Bent! Your abs are like a 6LDK apartment!
ダンベルカール！ ハンマーカール！ 二頭がいいね！ チョモランマ！
Dumbbell Curl! Hammer Curl! Nice biceps! Mount Everest!
プッシュアップ！ ベンチプレス！ 大胸筋が歩いてる！
Push-up! Bench Press! Your pecs are walking!
仕上がってるよ！ 仕上がってるよ！ 筋肉本舗！ はい、ズドーン！
You're lookin' good! You're lookin' good! Muscle Shop! Boom!
理想の自分を思い描いたら 今すぐ始めよトレーニング (イエス、マッスル！)
Once you've pictured your ideal self, start training right now! (Yes, muscle!)
ヤバめの現実何とかなるはず ダンベル両手にフリーウェイト (超マッチョ！)
You'll manage this crazy reality. Free weights in both hands! (Super macho!)
焦りは禁物 無理しちゃ沈没 負荷のかけ方を調節 (そう、筋肉！)
Don't rush or you'll sink. Adjust the load! (That's right, muscles!)
限界10回ギリギリ全開 3セットしたらオーライ (ナイスポーズ！)
10 reps at your limit, full throttle. 3 sets and you're all right! (Nice pose!)
辛いこともある筋肉道 (筋肉道) モテモテボディがほしいの！
The path of muscle has its hardships (muscle path). I want a popular body!
綺麗なワタシに大変身 (大変身) 見てなさい！ (さい、さい、さい、はい、サイドチェストー！)
A complete transformation into a beautiful me! Just watch! (Side Chest!)
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたい
Please muscle, I want to be super popular.
お願いマッスル めっちゃ痩せたい、イェス！
Please muscle, I want to lose lots of weight, yes!
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたいなら
Please muscle, if you want to be super popular...
ウー！ (キレてるよ！) ハー！ (キレてるよ！) 筋肉にお願いだ！
Woo! (You're ripped!) Ha! (You're ripped!) I'm counting on my muscles!
レッグカール！ ハックリフト！ 泣く子も黙る大腿筋！
Leg Curl! Hack Lift! Quadriceps that'll shut up a crying baby!
バックプレス！ サイドレイズ！ 肩にちっちゃい重機のせてんのかい！
Back Press! Side Raise! Are you carrying a small bulldozer on your shoulders?!
ベントオーバー！ ラットプルダウン！ 背中に鬼神が宿ってる！
Bent-over Row! Lat Pulldown! There's a demon on your back!
仕上がってるよ！ 仕上がってるよ！ 頑張るあなたは美しい！
You're lookin' good! You're lookin' good! You're beautiful when you work hard!
昨日の今日では効果なくても とにかく続けよトレーニング (超マッスル！)
Even if there's no immediate effect, just keep training! (Super muscle!)
気分を変えたい？ 悩みすぎて辛い？ それならマシンでワークアウト (リフレッシュ！)
Want a mood change? Too stressed? Then work out on a machine! (Refresh!)
けど食べるの大切、筋肉の秘訣 食事で身体を建設 (ボディビルディング！)
But eating is important, that's the muscle secret. Build your body with food! (Bodybuilding!)
3日に1回？ 週に2〜3回？ 無理ないペースでオッケー！ (ナイスバルク！)
Once every 3 days? 2-3 times a week? A comfortable pace is OK! (Nice bulk!)
めげそうな時思い出して (思い出して) 努力が実になれば万緑
Remember when you're about to give up (remember) that hard work will blossom.
見せつけたいでしょ脚線美 (脚線美) 頑張ります？ (ます、ます、ます、はい、モストマスキュラー！)
You want to show off your shapely legs, right? Ready to try hard? (Most Muscular!)
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたい
Please muscle, I want to be super popular.
お願いマッスル めっちゃ痩せたい、イェス！
Please muscle, I want to lose lots of weight, yes!
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたいなら
Please muscle, if you want to be super popular...
ウー！ (キレてるよ！) ハー！ (キレてるよ！) 筋肉にお願いだ！
Woo! (You're ripped!) Ha! (You're ripped!) I'm counting on my muscles!
いくよ！ 今から私とトレーニング！
Here we go! Time to train with me!
足を肩幅分開いたら
Open your legs shoulder-width apart,
両手は頭の後ろにあげて
put both hands behind your head,
片足を軽く上げたら準備はOK！ (Yeah!)
lift one leg slightly, and you're ready! (Yeah!)
It's セットポジション！
It's the set position!
上げた足と逆の肘をくっつけ...
Touch the opposite elbow to the raised knee...
くっつけるように腹筋を
Contract your abs as if touching...
収縮！
Contract!
できたら戻して逆側も！
Once done, return and do the other side!
足と逆の肘を
Opposite leg and elbow...
くっつけるように腹筋を
Contract your abs as if touching...
収縮！
Contract!
できたら戻しても一回！
Once done, return and do it one more time!
足と逆の肘を
Opposite leg and elbow...
くっつけるように腹筋を
Contract your abs as if touching...
収縮！
Contract!
筋肉に
To the muscles...
お願いだ！
I'm begging you!
はい、サイドチェストーーー！
Yes, side chest!
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたい
Please Muscle, I want to be super popular
お願いマッスル
Please Muscle
めっちゃ痩せたい、イェー！
I want to lose so much weight, yeah!
お願いマッスル めっちゃモテたいなら
Please Muscle, if you want to be super popular
ウー！
Wooo!
キレてるよ！
You're looking ripped!
筋肉にお願いだ
I'm begging the muscles
ヒップレイズ！
Hip raise!
サイドベント！
Side bend!
腹筋板チョコバレンタイン！
Abs like a chocolate bar Valentine!
ダンベルカール！
Dumbbell curl!
ハンマーカール！
Hammer curl!
これが二頭の新時代...
This is the new era of biceps...
プッシュアップ！
Push up!
ベンチプレス！
Bench press!
はじ切れそうな大胸筋！
Pectorals about to burst!
サイドクランチ！
Side crunch!
ハイクリーン！
High clean!
出たな！プロポーションおばけ！
There it is! A proportion monster!
レッグカール！
Leg curl!
ハックリフト！
Hack lift!
ザッツアグレート大腿筋！
That's a great quadriceps!
バックプレス！
Back press!
サイドレイズ！
Side raise!
とれたて新鮮肩メロン！
Freshly picked shoulder melons!
ベントオーバー！
Bent over!
ラットプルダウン！
Lat pulldown!
背中に世界を背負ってる！
Carrying the world on your back!
仕上がってるよ！
Looking finished!
頑張るあなたは美しい！
You who work hard are beautiful!
お願いマッスル
Please Muscle
BANG! BANG! バカンス！
BANG! BANG! Vacance!
シャワー浴びて真夜中
In the middle of the night after a shower
クーラーのリモコン抱きしめ
Hugging the air conditioner's remote control
せいぜい言って去年の夏
At most, talking about last summer
バイクの免許欲しいな
I want a motorcycle license
そしたらバイクもしな
And if I get it, a bike too
でも結局うだうだしてたおととしの夏
But in the end, I just lazed around the summer before last
バカンスって言葉の半分は
Half of the word "vacance"
バカンバカンバカン
Is "bakan bakan bakan"
どうせバカなら元気なバカがいい
If I'm going to be a fool anyway, I'd rather be a lively one
Baby BANG! BANG! 裸足でGO NOW
Baby BANG! BANG! Go barefoot now
人類の進化に逆らって
Against the evolution of mankind
Baby BANG! BANG! おバカ面で
Baby BANG! BANG! With a foolish face
スーツで海に飛び込んで
Jumping into the sea in a suit
じゃあ太陽と打ち合わせしよう
So, let's have a meeting with the sun
男前だね 木村くん
Looking handsome, Kimura-kun
当たり前だよ 前田さん
Of course, Maeda-san
前田さんなんてうちにはいない
There's no such person as Maeda-san at my place
マジで？
Really?
バイクの免許欲しいな
I want a motorcycle license
だけど歯医者へも行かなきゃ
But I also have to go to the dentist
でも結局うだうだしそう今年の夏も
But I'll probably end up lazing around this summer too
稲垣って名字の半分は
Half of the surname "Inagaki"
ガキガキガキ
Is "gaki gaki gaki"
どうせガキなら迷惑なガキでいい
If I'm going to be a brat anyway, I'd rather be an annoying one
Baby BANG! BANG! 裸足でGO NOW
Baby BANG! BANG! Go barefoot now
面目もプライドも投げ捨てて
Throwing away honor and pride
Baby BANG! BANG! おバカ面で
Baby BANG! BANG! With a foolish face
海パンで国際線乗っちゃって
Taking an international flight in swimming trunks
もう恋なんて現地調達
Love is something to be procured on the spot
計画どおりなんか進まない
Nothing goes according to plan
それがバカのバカ
That's the fool's fool
うちに着くまで元気なバカでいい
It's fine to be a lively fool until getting home
Baby BANG! BANG! 裸足でGO NOW
Baby BANG! BANG! Go barefoot now
サングラスたまにのけちゃって
Taking off the sunglasses once in a while
Baby BANG! BANG! おバカ面で
Baby BANG! BANG! With a foolish face
BANG! BANG! バカンス! おバカづらで
BANG! BANG! Vacance! With a silly look on our faces
Tシャツの裾 結んじゃって
Tying up the hem of my T-shirt
さあ写真は 基本Vサインで
Come on, the photo is basically a V-sign
後悔と反省がお土産
Regret and self-reflection are my souvenirs
キャットラビング 作詞・作曲 香椎モイミ
Cat Loving - Lyrics/Composition: Kashii Moimi
痛いことは嫌いですが
I dislike things that hurt, but
君の手の平は嫌いじゃないかな
I don't think I dislike your palm.
言葉は飴玉みたいに
Words, like hard candies,
甘く広がってココロ満たす
spread sweetly and fill my heart.
鳴呼 全然分かってない
Ah, you don't understand at all.
永遠に言う通り
Obeying you forever,
完全にフェアじゃない
it's not fair at all.
(どこにいても)
(Wherever I am)
鳴呼 「何で？」は効いてない
Ah, "Why?" doesn't work.
もっともっとあの子みたいに 可愛くならなくちゃ
I have to become even cuter, more like that girl.
愛情は聡明に 傷痕はHow many?
Love is clever, how many scars are there?
もう体堕 痛いののだって 分かんなくなる
Already, even the pain of degradation becomes unrecognizable.
延命マタタビ 週二ご褒美
Life-prolonging silver vine, rewards twice a week.
「もう嫌んなった」って 離されないように
So that I won't be let go of even if I say "I've had enough."
今日だってちゃんと内緒の毛繕い
Today, too, I'm grooming myself in secret.
にゃんって良い子にするから 愛して
I'll be a good girl and go "nyan," so love me.
Everybody
Today is rubbing day
Get it Get it This is my courtship
Any Any Anytime is Fine with me
Gimme Gimme Love me, my darling
会いたいを間違いなんて皆は言う
Everyone says wanting to see you is a mistake,
取り憑かれているって
and that I'm possessed.
ならこの胸で疼く
Then, the aching in this chest,
締め付けるような切なさは何なの？
what is this tightening sadness?
選ぶ言葉と戸惑う指先
The words I choose and my hesitating fingertips,
端正な横顔 (私しか知らない)
your handsome profile (only I know it).
鳴呼 ランダムご機嫌
Ah, your random moods.
もしかして今日は 優しく撫でてくれるのかな？
Maybe you'll pet me gently today?
君のソレが耐えられるの
The person who can endure that of yours,
生涯で私だけなんだよね
is only me in my whole life, right?
あからさまに カラダまさに
Obviously, my body is exactly...
「もう嫌だ」って 離れられないよね
unable to leave even if I say "I've had enough."
そうだよね？
Isn't that right?
感情は上々に 歌唱は少々に
Feelings are at their peak, singing just a little.
もうLieも春のように 転がせば良い
I can just roll lies along like the spring.
相挨の匂いだって凌ぐのだ
I'll even overcome the scent of a lover.
もう噛んだって叱られるだけだし
Even if I bite, I'll just be scolded anyway.
今日だってちゃんとお膝で大人しく
Today, too, I'll be quiet on your lap,
にゃんってお好きなように
go "nyan," and do as you please.
完全淘汰して
Completely eliminate me.
うわー！えい！みんな見て！
Wow! Hey! Everyone, look!
キャットラビングからのー！ノエちゃんなんとね、
Following Cat Loving...! Noel-chan is actually,
猫耳つけております！
wearing cat ears!
つけ猫耳！
Fake cat ears!
いっぱいスクショ撮ってね！イェーイ！
Take lots of screenshots! Yay!
はぁ...ちょっといつもと違うようなね、
Phew... I sang a song that's a bit different from usual,
曲を歌ってヒィヒィなんですけど。
and I'm a bit out of breath.
あ、でも可愛いですね。
Ah, but it's cute.
あ、でも可愛いけど、ちょっと色々まだまだありますので。
Ah, it's cute, but there's still a lot more to come.
ちょ、ちょっとね、付け耳をとってきますので。
So, I'm going to go take off the ears.
しばし、しばしお待ちください。
Please wait a moment.
取れたかなーと、はい！
Did I get them? Yes!
いや、ちょっとなんか名残惜しいんですけど、
Well, I feel a bit sad to let them go, but
この衣装はですね、ブライト衣装になっております！
this outfit is the Bright Costume!
さっきまで水着着てたから、
I was wearing a swimsuit until just now,
ちょっとなんか暑いなーって感じなんですけど、
so I'm feeling a bit hot.
まあこれからね、もっともっと熱い夏にしていきましょう！
But let's make this summer even hotter from now on!
そして団員さん、他にも気づいたところありますよね？
And Knight-cups, you've noticed other things too, right?
そう、見てください、このステージ！
That's right, look at this stage!
すげー！
It's amazing!
皆さん初めて見たと思いますけど。
I think it's the first time you've seen it.
今回、夏のこの4周年ライブに向けて
For this summer's 4th anniversary live,
ステージを作っていただきました！ありがとうございます！
they built this stage for me! Thank you so much!
しかもなんと上に団員さんもいるんですよ！
And what's more, there are Knight-cups up there too!
なんかね、栗食べてるね。
They're eating chestnuts.
いや、可愛い、モグモグしてるね。
So cute, they're munching away.
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
イェーイ！団員さん、そこから見守っててね！あー可愛い。
Yay! Knight-cups, watch over me from there! Ah, so cute.
いや、すごい特等席からノエちゃんの事を見守ってくれててありがとう。
Thank you for watching over me from such a great vantage point.
可愛いねー。
So cute.
あのー団員さんね、是非是非、
Um, Knight-cups, please,
あのご飯食べたりね、色々しながら
while eating your meals and doing various things,
ノエちゃんのライブ楽しんでください！
please enjoy Noel-chan's live!
もちろんね、ハッシュタグで呟くのも忘れずに！
And of course, don't forget to tweet with the hashtag!
...たいなって思うんですけど。じゃあちょっと着替えますかね。
...is what I was thinking. Alright, let's change outfits then.
ちょっと暑いんでね。ちょっと色々衣装もあるので、ではちょっと1回、ペッ！
It's a bit hot, you see. And I have various outfits, so... here we go, ppeh!
ちょっとノエちゃんの着替えてるとこ見ないで！
Hey, don't look while Noe-chan is changing!
いつでも大丈夫だよ。はーい！
I'm ready anytime. Okay!
ということで、年ス衣装になりましたー！イェーイ！
And so, I've changed into my annual outfit! Yay!
ちょっとね、さっきよりも涼しげな感じになっておるんですけど...
It feels a bit more refreshing than the previous one...
次はね、どんな曲を歌うのか、そして、もしかして、誰かと歌うかも？
Next, what kind of song will I sing? And maybe, I'll sing with someone?
ということでね、ぜひあの、最後まで聴いてってくださーい！
So, please stay tuned until the very end!
ライブまだまだ続くよ。それじゃ、歌います！
The live is still going on. Well then, I'll sing!
PAKUっとしたいわ 端から端まで結ばれたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to be tied together from end to end
PAKUっとしたいわ 指先と言葉で伝えたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to tell you with my fingertips and words
PAKUっとしたいわ わがままかもしれないアンサーで
I want to take a BITE, with an answer that might be selfish
PAKUっとしたいわ どっちもどっちにしたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to make them both the same
ただただ問答 間違ってんのはどっち？ え、スマイルは0円です
Just a back and forth, which one is wrong? Oh, smiles are free of charge
でも心はすり減ってくようです
But my heart seems to be wearing down
あーあ 満身創痍 意気消沈 ローリンサンダー 完徹ムービング
Ah, battered and bruised, dispirited, rolling thunder, all-nighter moving
動乱ペンティ 本当のフェイスに誰か気付いてんだ
Upheaval penty, someone's noticed my real face
冗談めいた言葉で案外本心です
With joking words, it's actually my true feelings
だって歌ってそういうもんでしょってネットの掲示板で読んだよ
Because that's what singing is all about, I read it on an online message board
腐ってるんじゃなんとか生きてけそうかも知れない
If I'm rotten, I might be able to survive somehow
どうかと思うけどこれが私 あー言えばこう言う
I wonder about it, but this is me, always having a comeback
PAKUっとしたいわ 端から端まで結ばれたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to be tied together from end to end
PAKUっとしたいわ 指先と言葉で伝えたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to tell you with my fingertips and words
PAKUっとしたいわ わがままかもしれないアンサーで
I want to take a BITE, with an answer that might be selfish
PAKUっとしたいわ どっちもどっちにしたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to make them both the same
てかてか繰り出すハリセンデレンダ 動き取れないな怠惰タイダ
Anyway, launching a paper fan barrage, I can't move, laziness, laziness
いつ立つ摩天楼 今夜ハトディスコミュニケーション マイゴージャ
When will the skyscraper stand? Tonight, pigeon-discommunication, my gorge
あーあ 全然ないなバケーション 完徹ルーティン 生絞りの柑橘
Ah, no vacation at all, all-nighter routine, fresh-squeezed citrus
ゲームオンディスナンデス 気を抜いたら9%です
Game on, this is it, if I let my guard down, it's 9%
早期解決だって言わない問題です つーか実感持って終わってる
It's a problem I won't say can be solved quickly, I mean, it's already over with a sense of reality
現在進行形かも フラットな感情どっか行っちゃった
Maybe in progress, my flat emotions have gone somewhere
宝物は何？捨てるつもりもないのにさ あー言えばこう言う
What's the treasure? I have no intention of throwing it away, but... always having a comeback
PAKUっとしたいわ 端から端まで結ばれたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to be tied together from end to end
PAKUっとしたいわ 指先と言葉で伝えたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to tell you with my fingertips and words
PAKUっとしたいわ わがままかもしれないアンサーで
I want to take a BITE, with an answer that might be selfish
PAKUっとしたいわ どっちもどっちにしたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to make them both the same
PAKUっとしたいわ 音から意味まで結ばれたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to be tied together from sound to meaning
PAKUっとしたいわ 確かなことだけ見つからないや
I want to take a BITE, only certain things cannot be found
PAKUっとしたいわ おのおのから繋がるアンサーで
I want to take a BITE, with an answer connecting from each other
PAKUっとしたいわ どっちもどっちにしたいな
I want to take a BITE, I want to make them both the same
キラキラ光ってるはずなんだ ワールドワイドワンダー
It's supposed to be sparkling, World Wide Wonder
キャ、キャ、キャっ飛ばしてオーバーペースで 困り毎の毎日だ
Ki-ki-kicking it away at over-pace, everyday is full of trouble
頭こんがらがってウォーニング ウォーニング
Head getting all tangled up, Warning, Warning
でっかい月の上にウサギがいるんだけど
There's a rabbit on top of the big moon
宇宙旅行にパスポートっていりますか？
Do I need a passport for space travel?
僕らが歩いていく世界の 明日はどんな色？
What color will tomorrow be in the world we walk through?
君と僕で描いていく二人色 鮮やか
The color of us two that you and I paint together, so vivid
チェックメイト君をチェックメイト 会いたい時に会いにいくよ
Checkmate, checkmate you, I'll come to see you when I want to see you
地球の裏から夢の中まで
From the other side of the Earth to inside my dreams
ヒラヒラスカートが揺れる
The fluttering skirt sways
エスコート君をエスコート
Escort, escort you
マニュアル通りじゃつまんないでしょ？
Following the manual is boring, right?
不安もあったけど希望があるってこと
There was anxiety, but there's hope
キラキラ光ってるはずなんだ
It's supposed to be sparkling
エマージェンシーちゃん なんでもありのアイドルだ
Emergency-chan, an idol who can do anything
常識もぐらついちゃってパニックパニック
Even common sense is wobbling, Panic, Panic
深海 海の底でマーメイドが恋をしたって
At the bottom of the deep sea, a mermaid fell in love
嘘か本当か確かめに来ませんか？
Won't you come and see if it's a lie or the truth?
僕らの暮らしてる世界は 一人一人ひとつの色
The world we live in is a single color for each and every person
それはお父さんお母さんの愛の色 鮮やか
That's the color of father and mother's love, so vivid
Checkmate 君を Checkmate
Checkmate, you, checkmate
雨降り天気でも 会いに行くよ
Even if it's rainy weather, I'll go to meet you
果報が来るまで寝とけばいいってマジ？
Is it true that it's okay to sleep until good luck comes?
いやいや 待てるわけなくて
No no, there's no way I can wait
絶好調 ずっと絶好調
In peak condition, always in peak condition
片道切符で構わないでしょ？
A one-way ticket is fine, right?
無理も通せば道理がなんとやら
If you push through the impossible, reason will somehow follow
飛べる気がしてるんだ
I feel like I can fly
胸の奥がキュッとなる
My chest feels a tightening sensation
消えない 消せない 過去も笑えるように
So I can laugh even at the past that won't fade or disappear
未来が僕らを呼んでる
The future is calling us
ほら 踊れる曲を躍ろうぜ
Look, let's dance to a danceable tune
楽しむが勝ち
The one who enjoys it wins
Checkmate 君を Checkmate
Checkmate, you, checkmate
会いたい時には会いに行くよ
When I want to see you, I'll go to meet you
机の奥から22世紀まで
From the back of the desk to the 22nd century
フラフラ 旅してる途中
Right in the middle of a wandering journey
Escort 君を Escort
Escort, you, escort
マニュアル通りじゃつまんないでしょ？
Doing it by the manual is boring, right?
不安の数だけ希望があるってこと
There's as much hope as there is anxiety
飛べる気がしてる
I feel like I can fly
キラキラ 光ってるはずなんだ
I should be shining brightly
マーシャル・マキシマイザー
Marshall Maximizer
相対実験に付き合う朝 14ポンドを笑え
A morning spent on relative experiments, laugh at the 14 pounds
レッド どうしようもないけど 気狂い人のふりをしている君を見ている
Red, it's hopeless, but I'm watching you pretend to be a madman
あめんどだったから切り捨てた 40サイズをさらば
It was troublesome, so I cut it out, farewell to the 40 size
グッバイ 申し訳ないけど すれ違うものに無為に期待を背負わしている
Goodbye, I'm sorry, but I'm pointlessly burdening those I pass with expectations
野放図な煩脳 目に焼き付いた残像 まるで無敵人生 最大効率 約する賛賞さ
Unrestrained worldly desires, an afterimage burned into my eyes, like an invincible life, maximum efficiency, a promised praise
食べて すぐ寝て 牛になる
Eat, sleep right away, and turn into a cow
起きて また寝て 非人なし
Wake up, sleep again, no longer human
Maximizer Maximizer 寄せ合い 燃やしちゃって
Maximizer, Maximizer, gathering and burning it up
ヘビだ強行 なんてこった 死んでしまうわ
It's a snake enforcement, oh my god, I'm going to die
恨み辛み天窓 雁字搦め
Grudges and bitterness through the skylight, bound hand and foot
Maximizer Maximizer 吐き出しちゃいな
Maximizer, Maximizer, just spit it out
取り戻したい 全部 現金 落ちろ 落ちるわ
I want to get it all back, all of it, cash, fall down, I'm falling
暗み天窓 世界は Faraway
Skylight in the darkness, the world is faraway
相対実験に繰り出すアラーム 94ポンドを笑え
An alarm setting off for relative experiments, laugh at the 94 pounds
レッド どうしようもないから 気狂い人の真似をしている君へ
Red, because there's nothing that can be done, to you who are imitating a madman
簡単なこと無視していたいなら足りないわ
If you want to keep ignoring simple things, it's not enough
申し訳ないなら すでにアートに不認可はまとまらないわ
If you're sorry, then non-recognition in art won't be settled already
五臓六腑の煩脳 手に焼き付いた残像 まるで無敵人間 最小降伏 弾頭台
The desires of my internal organs, an afterimage burned into my hand, like an invincible human, minimum surrender, on the guillotine
食べて すぐ寝て 牛になる
Eat, sleep right away, and turn into a cow
起きて また寝て 非人なし
Wake up, sleep again, no longer human
舞い散るまま Maximizer 寄せ合い 焦がしちゃって
As it scatters, Maximizer, gathering and scorching it
ヘビだ強行 なんてこった 生きてしまうわ
It's a snake enforcement, oh my god, I'm going to live
恨み辛み天窓 雁字搦め
Grudges and bitterness through the skylight, bound hand and foot
Maximizer Maximizer 寄せ合い 燃やしちゃって
Maximizer, Maximizer, gathering and burning it up
ヘビだ強行 なんてこった 死んでしまうわ
It's a snake enforcement, oh my god, I'm going to die
恨み辛み天窓 雁字搦め
Grudges and bitterness through the skylight, bound hand and foot
Maximizer Maximizer 吐き出しちゃいな
Maximizer, Maximizer, just spit it out
取り戻したい 全部 現金 落ちろ 落ちるわ
I want to get it all back, all of it, cash, fall down, I'm falling
暗み天窓 世界は Faraway
Skylight in the darkness, the world is faraway
Maximizer Maximizer
アイドル
作詞・作曲: Ayase
Idol
Lyrics/Composition: Ayase
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Media stirred up by that invincible smile
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
Want to know that mysterious secret
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even her flaws are within her area
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, perfect and a liar
天才的なアイドル様
Are a genius-like idol
今日何食べた？好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
Where do you go when you go out to play?
何も食べてない、それは内緒
I haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
Dodging every question I'm asked
そう淡々と、だけど燦々と
So calmly, yet so brilliantly
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
Secrets that seem visible but aren't taste like honey
あれもないないない
Not that, no, no, no
これもないないない
Not this, no, no, no
好きなタイプは？相手は？さあ答えて
What's your type? Who is it? Come on, answer
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ」
"I don't really know what it's like to fall in love."
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Can't tell if it's a lie or the truth
そんな言葉にまた一人堕ちる
One more person falls for those words
また好きにさせる
Making them love you again
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone is getting their eyes stolen
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You're the perfect, ultimate idol
金婚際現れない
Never to appear again
一番星の生まれ変わり
The reincarnation of the brightest star
その笑顔で「愛してる」で
With that smile, with an "I love you"
誰もかれも虜にしていく
You make everyone your captive
その瞳がその言葉が
Those eyes, those words
嘘でもそれは完全な愛
Even if they're lies, it's perfect love
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special
我々は端からおまけです
We were just extras from the start
お星様の引き立て役Bです
We're just Supporting Role B to the star
すべてがあの子のおかげなわけない
It's not like everything is thanks to her
洒落臭い妬み嫉妬なんてないわけがない
There's no way there isn't annoying envy and jealousy
これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない
Because it's not a joke, I can't forgive it
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない
I can't forgive you for not being perfect
自分許せない
I can't forgive myself
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't acknowledge anyone but you, the strongest
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes and worships
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Truly the strongest, invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない
Not a single weakness to be found
一番星を宿している
Carrying the brightest star within
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
You must never, ever show any weakness
知りたくないとこは見せずに
Without showing things they don't want to know
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
You have to be one of a kind, no, no
それこそが本物のアイ
That is what true love is
特異の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Rousing the media with that unique smile
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Only keeping this secret hidden
「愛してる」と嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on the lie of "I love you"
これこそ私なりの愛だ
This is my own kind of love
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the flowing sweat is beautiful aqua
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids hiding rubies
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Maria
そう、嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are the ultimate love
誰かに愛されたことも
Having been loved by someone
誰かのこと愛したこともない
Or having ever loved someone
そんな私の嘘が
Those lies of mine
いつか本当になること信じてる
I believe that one day they'll become the truth
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
One day I'll surely have everything
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
Yes, I'm such a greedy idol
等身大でみんなのこと
With my true self, everyone
ちゃんと愛したいから
Because I want to love you properly
今日も嘘をつくの
I tell lies again today
この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
Praying for the day these words come true
それでもまだ
Even so, I still
君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
Couldn't say it to you and you, but...
ああやっと言えた
Ah, I finally said it
これは絶対嘘じゃない
This is definitely not a lie
愛してる
I love you
Deep in Abyss
作詞: hotaru
作曲: kanadeYUK・Masahiro "Godspeed" Aoki
Deep in Abyss
Lyrics: hotaru
Composition: kanadeYUK・Masahiro "Godspeed" Aoki
誰もが抗えずに潜っていく
Everyone dives in without resisting
その目をともしびより輝かせて
Making those eyes shine brighter than a light
目指す先は深く
The destination is deep
まっすぐに迷い込む
Wandering straight in
口開けた奈落の罠
The trap of the abyss with its mouth wide open
真実のあとを追いかけよう
Let's chase after the truth
今答えが見つかるなら
If the answer can be found now
全部失くしてもいい
It's fine to lose everything
その声を離さないように
So as not to let go of that voice
木霊がまだ響いてる
The echo is still resonating
羅針盤はずっと闇を指したまま逃げ場のない
The compass keeps pointing to darkness, with no place to run
報い
Retribution
それが呪いでも
Even if that's a curse
鼓動は本物
The heartbeat is real
二度と憧れは
The longing will never
止まらない
stop again.
かたち
Shape
歌声の止む時は
When the singing stops,
運命の終わり
it's the end of destiny.
そっとだけ決めていた
I had quietly decided,
行方はわからない
though I don't know the destination.
君をなぞるほど
The more I trace you,
焦がれてるのに
the more I yearn for you.
憧れの輪郭は
The outline of my longing
遠ざかってくみたい
seems to be fading away.
溢れるよ ほら手のひら
It's overflowing, look, in my palm.
握り返してくれ
Please squeeze back.
痛みと痛み 取り替えよう
Let's exchange pain for pain.
糧にすんだ 仲間の欠片
Turning the fragments of friends into nourishment.
すべて傷ついても僕は
Even if I'm completely hurt,
形どっていく
I will keep shaping it.
目覚めの叫びで
With the cry of awakening,
行こう
let's go.
ずっと響かせよう
Let's make it echo forever.
旅の左手、最果ての右手
Traveler's Left Hand, Right Hand at the End
空に浮かんでる 光る波を
Floating in the sky, the shining waves...
束ねて道の 橋を駆けよう
Gather them and let's run across the bridge of our path.
危うい足場 滑るスロープ
Precarious footing, a slippery slope.
過去と未来の 道標
The signpost of the past and the future.
君の左手 僕の右手をつないで
Your left hand and my right hand, joined together.
つなげて 始めよう
Connected, let's begin.
いつもそばにいるよ
I'm always by your side.
過去も今も未来も
The past, the present, and the future.
だから迷わずに 歩いていこう
So let's walk forward without hesitation.
色とりどりの夢 重ねて
Layering our colorful dreams,
明日はどこに向かう
where is tomorrow headed?
君と一緒にいれたら
If I can be with you,
世界は輝きだすよ
the world starts to shine.
最果ての地に咲く 花を探そう
Let's find the flower that blooms at the ends of the earth.
夜明けが近い 薄明かりに
Dawn is near. In the dim light,
耳を澄ませば 風が歌う
if you listen closely, the wind sings.
秘密を教えて 覗くスコープ
Tell me a secret. Looking through the scope,
祈る奇跡が 叶うなら
if the miracle I pray for comes true...
二人の装備は 身軽じゃなきゃね
Our equipment must be light.
希望と絆が あればいい
Hope and bonds are all we need.
何もなくっていいよ
We don't need anything.
星も空も光も
Not the stars, the sky, or the light.
君の声を頼りに さあ行こう
Relying only on your voice, let's go.
止まらない憧れ 重ねて
Layering our unstoppable longing,
明日は続いていく
tomorrow continues.
帰り道さえ見えない
Let's cross the world where
世界を超えて行こうよ
even the way back is unseen.
見果てぬ夢に咲く 花を探そう
Let's find the flower that blooms in our endless dreams.
柔らかな心に
The will dwelling
宿る意思は強く
in a soft heart is strong.
鋼のように 結ばれた思い
Thoughts bound together like steel.
飛んでいけ どこまでも
Fly away, as far as it goes.
天まで高く
High up to the heavens
色とりどりの夢 重ねて
Layering colorful dreams,
明日はどこに向かう
where will we head tomorrow?
君と一緒にいれたら
If I can be with you,
世界は輝きだすよ
the world will start to shine.
最果ての地に咲く花を探そう
Let's find the flower that blooms at the ends of the earth.
変わらないもの
Things That Never Change
帰り道ふざけて歩いた
On the way home, we walked while fooling around
訳もなく君を怒らせた
and I made you angry for no reason.
色んな君の顔を見たかったんだ
I wanted to see all kinds of expressions on your face.
大きな瞳が 泣きそうな声が
Your big eyes, your voice that sounded like you're about to cry,
今も僕の胸を締め付ける
they still tighten my chest even now.
すれ違う人の中で 君を追いかけた
Among the passing people, I chased after you.
変わらないもの 探していた
I was looking for things that never change.
あの日の君を 忘れはしない
I will never forget you as you were on that day.
時を越えてく 思いがある
There are feelings that transcend time.
僕は今すぐ 君に会いたい
I want to see you right now.
街灯にぶら下げた想い
The feelings hung on the streetlights,
いつも君には渡せなかった
I could never give them to you.
夜は僕たちを遠ざけていったね
The night kept drifting us apart, didn't it?
見えない心で 嘘ついた声が
With an invisible heart, the voice that lied,
今も僕の胸に響いている
it's still echoing in my chest even now.
彷徨う時の中で
Within the wandering time,
君と恋をした
I fell in love with you.
変わらないもの 探していた
I was looking for things that never change.
あの日見つけた 知らない場所へ
To that unknown place we found that day,
君と二人で 行けるのなら
if the two of us can go there together,
僕は何度も 生まれ変われる
I can be reborn again and again.
形ないもの 抱きしめていた
I was embracing things without form.
壊れる音も 聞こえないまま
Without even hearing the sound of them breaking,
君と歩いた 同じ道に
on the same path I walked with you,
今も灯りは 照らし続ける
the light continues to shine even now.
変わらないもの 探していた
I was looking for something that wouldn't change
あの日の君を 忘れはしない
I won't forget you as you were that day
時を越えてく 思いがある
There's a feeling that transcends time
僕は今すぐ 君に会いたい
I want to see you right now
あー、もうすっかり夜になっちまった。
Ah... it's already completely night.
あ、なんかすごいね、しみじみした。
Ah, I'm feeling quite sentimental somehow.
なんか夏の夜って気持ちになっているんですが、
It feels like a summer night, but...
皆さん、ちょっとね、びっくりするようなことを今から言うので
Everyone, I'm about to say something a bit surprising, so...
ちょっと心臓…ちょっと破裂しないでくださいね。
...please don't let your hearts... don't let them burst, okay?
なんと団長ね、あの、結構周年やら誕生日で
You see, every anniversary or birthday...
毎回お披露目してるものがあるんですけど、何だと思いますか？
...there's something I always reveal, but what do you think it is?
んんん…つっつっつんっ！
Mmm... *drumroll*!
そうです！今回もね、新曲を発表したいと思います！イェーイ！
That's right! I'm going to announce a new song this time too! Yay!
えっと、今回ですね、あの、発表する曲なんですけど、
Um, the song I'm announcing this time...
タイトルが「ラフミーテンダー」という曲になっておりまして、
...the title is "Love Me Tender"...
作詞、作曲、編曲がなんと、あの有名な
And the lyrics, composition, and arrangement are by...
TOKOTOKOさんこと西沢さんPに作っていただきました！
...none other than the famous TOKOTOKO, also known as Nishizawasan-P!
ありがとうございます！やったー！
Thank you so much! Yay!
いやね、もう本当にいい神曲いっぱいあるんですけど、
I mean, there are so many truly amazing songs,
今回のライブでスバちゃんと歌った「ワールドワイドワンダー」がね、
but "World Wide Wonder," which I sang with Suba-chan during this live,
あの、西沢さんPの曲なんですけど、
...is also a song by Nishizawasan-P.
なんでスバちゃんと歌ったかというと、
The reason I sang it with Suba-chan is because...
団長一番好きな曲になるんですよね、西沢さんPの曲で一番好きなんですが、
...it's my absolute favorite song by Nishizawasan-P.
まあ団長、まあスバちゃんとね、歌いたかったっていうのはあるんだけど、
Well, of course I wanted to sing with Suba-chan,
一番は団長がスバちゃんのことを、まあちょっと、最推しになったきっかけの…
but the main reason is that it was the catalyst for me becoming a huge Subaru fan...
…かの有名なスバちゃんのライブがあるんですけど、
...which was a certain famous live of Suba-chan's.
そこでね、団長もう全部がね好きだったんだけど、特に…
I loved everything about it, but especially...
…あの「夜もすがら君想ふ」っていう西沢さんPの曲を
...that song "Yomosugara Kimi Omou" by Nishizawasan-P,
スバちゃんが、あの、歌って踊ってしてたとこにちょっと惚れてしまったんでね。
the way Suba-chan sang and danced to it, I just fell in love with it.
そういうちょっと点と点が結び合うみたいな感じで、
So, in a way, it felt like the dots were finally connecting,
あの、スバちゃんと歌わせていただきました。
and I was able to sing it with Suba-chan.
そんな感じで色々な縁がありまして、
With all those connections coming together,
今回、はい、新曲作っていただいたので早速、
I had this new song written for me, so...
あの、皆さんにお披露目したいと思います！
...I'd like to perform it for everyone right away!
それでは聴いてください、「ラフミーテンダー」！
Please listen: "Love Me Tender"!
君に会いたい
I want to see you
もっとちゃんと ちとちゃんと 時間もかけて
More properly, a bit properly, taking time
話せたらいいのに
I wish I could talk to you
いつも僕は焦ってばっか 言いたいことの
I'm always just in a rush, not even half
半分も言えなくて
of what I want to say gets out
あのね、七転び八起きなんて言うけど
You know, they say "fall seven times, stand up eight,"
一回でも起きれたら上等
but even standing up once is a feat
でもね、やると決めるって自分で知ってる
But you know, I know myself—when I decide to do it, I do
そうだ 答えはシンプルで
That's right, the answer is simple
昨日の失敗も 明日の憂鬱も 君と話せば笑い話になる
Yesterday's failures and tomorrow's blues, talking to you turns them into a funny story
どこにいても 何をしてても 声は飛んでいく 君の元へ
Wherever I am, whatever I'm doing, my voice flies to where you are
どんより雨降りも しんぼり泣き虫も 君にかかれば ほらキラキラ光る
A gloomy downpour or a dejected crybaby, in your hands, look, they sparkle and shine
嬉しい楽しいがもっと増えていく
The happy and the fun just keep increasing
無邪気な子供のように抱きしめて
Hold me tight like an innocent child
君に会いたい
I want to see you
位置についてよーいドンで 周回遅れで
Ready, set, go! A full lap behind
明日は二周回遅れ？
Tomorrow, will I be two laps behind?
あのね、理由もなく陽気になる日は
You know, on days I feel cheerful for no reason...
心が疲れてる証拠
Evidence that the heart is tired
でもね、笑う門には福もみに来てるかもって
But you know, maybe good fortune is coming to see those who smile
Oh Baby, What a Beautiful Day
うろ覚えな歌詞も
Vaguely remembered lyrics too
曖昧なメロディも
And vague melodies too
君と歌えばほら名曲になる
If I sing with you, look, it becomes a masterpiece
友達以上か未満より
Rather than more or less than friends
名前のない特別な距離
An unnamed special distance
昨日の失敗も
Yesterday's failures too
明日の憂鬱も
And tomorrow's gloom too
君と話せば笑い話になる
If I talk with you, it becomes a funny story
どこにいても何をしてても
Wherever I am, whatever I'm doing
声は飛んでく 君の方へ
My voice flies towards you
どしゃ降り雨降りも
Even in a downpour
しょんぼり泣き虫も
And even when I'm a mopey crybaby
君にかかればほらキラキラ光る
When it comes to you, look, it shines brightly
嬉しい楽しいがもっと増えてく
Happiness and fun keep increasing
無邪気な子供のように抱きしめて
Embrace me like an innocent child
I want you all day, all night
君に会いたい
I want to see you
はい、いかがでしたか？ ラフミーテンダーでした！
Yes, how was it? That was 'Love Me Tender'!
あー、いや本当に、この日のためにね、ちょっと本当に書き下ろしていただいたので、ちょっと皆さんにお披露目できてよかったです。
Ah, no really, it was written specifically for today, so I'm glad I could show it to everyone.
でね、ちょっとノエちゃんま最後ね、ちょっとすごいエモエモな団員さんに届けるお曲を、あの、まだ1曲あるんですけど、
And so, Noel has one last, really emotional song to deliver to the Knights at the end, but...
その前にちょっと2点ほど、ちょっと忘れてたので、
Before that, there are a couple of things I forgot,
紹介というか、あの、いいですか？
so let me introduce them, if that's okay?
あの、ちょっとノエちゃん、今年も、あのモチのロン、4周年記念グッズ出します！それではドーン！
Noel is, of course, releasing 4th-anniversary merch this year too! So, here they are!
活動4周年記念
4th Anniversary of Activities
こちらです！はい、いやとってもいいでしょう？
Here it is! Yes, isn't it great?
では1個1個ちょっと紹介していきたいと思います。よし、じゃあちょっと、
Now, I'd like to introduce them one by one. Okay, then...
まずはですね、この中でちょっと団長的にイチ押しなんですけど、こちら。
First of all, this is the Knight Leader's top recommendation, this one.
ラバーマット
Rubber Mat
えーっと、ラバーマットですね。
Um, the rubber mat.
えっと、すごいかっこいい、あの、団長、ちょっとよくわかるかな？ 団長がね、ま、すごいかっこよくね、メイス持って戦ってるシーンなんですけど、
It's a really cool... can you see it well? It's a scene of the Knight Leader looking really cool, fighting with a mace...
なんと、ちょっと小さくね、あの団員さんも戦っています。
And, look, the Knights are fighting there in small detail too.
こちら、Rosuuri先生書き下ろしのラバーマットとなっております！
This is a rubber mat illustrated by Rosuuri-sensei!
いや、すごいかっこいい！そして、次は、こちら。
Wow, so cool! And next is this one.
白銀聖騎士団の団員証
Shirogane Order of Knights Membership Card
ドン！えっと、白銀聖騎士団の団員証！ いや、これね、めちゃめちゃ、これ作りたかったんよ！
Boom! The Shirogane Order of Knights membership card! Man, I really, really wanted to make this!
なんかさ、みんなさ、いろんなホロメンがさ、なんかそういうさ、証明書とか、
You know, seeing other Hololive members making things like certificates...
なんとか証みたいな、作ってるたびに、いや団長もこういうの作りてーなって思いながら、
...or IDs, I kept thinking, "I want to make something like that too."
はや4年。ちょっとね、お待たせしましたと。
And now, 4 years have passed. Sorry to have kept you waiting.
ちょっとお待たせしすぎたかもしれないんですが、こちらね、あの、ぜひ、あの、ゲットして、俺団員なんだぜーって、あの、アピールしてください。
I might have kept you waiting way too long, but please get this and brag about being a member.
そして、こちらを入れるね、あの、ドン！IDカードホルダーもセットに。
And, to put it in, boom! The ID card holder is also in the set.
IDカードホルダー
ID Card Holder
はい、ま、単品でも売ってるんですが、はい、ついておりますので、これもぜひぜひ要チェックでございます。
Yes, well, it's also sold individually, but it's included, so be sure to check this out too.
そして、こちら。ドン！
And next, this one. Boom!
団員さんぬいぐるみキーホルダー ver. 2023
Knight Plushie Keychain ver. 2023
えー、団員さんぬいぐるみキーホルダー ver.2023ということで、こちらめちゃめちゃかっこいいっしょ？
The Knight plushie keychain ver. 2023! This is super cool, right?
つよつよですよ、つよつよ。あの、ダブルでこうやってね、団長もメイス持ってるんですけど、
It's super strong, super strong. Like, both the Knight Leader and this Knight are holding maces...
このね団員さんもメイスを持ったかっこいいぬいぐるみになってるので、あの、ぜひゲットしてください。
...making it a really cool plushie, so please get one.
いや、本当に今回のテーマが、本当に戦う団長ということで、ま、団員さんも一緒に団員証だったりとか、
Really, this time's theme is the "Fighting Knight Leader," so the Knights have membership cards...
団員さんもね、つよつよな恰好したりとかっていう感じで、
...and are dressed up all tough.
いや、4年たったかもね、4年たったからそろそろ強くなろうということで、ええ、あのぜひゲットしてみてください。
Well, 4 years have passed, so I thought it's about time to get stronger. So, please try to get them.
そして、あの、今回、あのボイスも出ます！ ドン！
And, this time, there's also a voice pack! Boom!
記念ボイス
ASMRボイス「団長の膝枕でお昼寝♡」
Commemorative Voice Pack
ASMR Voice 'Nap on the Knight Leader's Lap♡'
あの、こちらASMRボイス、団長の膝枕…あ、団長の膝枕でお昼寝ということでね、あの、ぜひぜひ。
This ASMR voice pack, "Nap on the Knight Leader's Lap," so please check it out.
ちょっとこれね、内容恥ずかしいので、あの、ぜひ聞いた人の、はい、秘密ということで、よろしくお願いします。
The content is a bit embarrassing, so let's keep it a secret between those who listen to it. Thank you.
はい、ということでね、あのフルセットもあるんですが、フルセットは、ま、こちらになります！
Yes, and so, there's also a full set, and the full set is this!
活動4周年記念フルセット
4th Anniversary Activity Full Set
はい、で、今回フルセットを購入していただいた方に特典二つあります。ちょっとすごいボリューミーでごめんね。
Yes, and there are two bonuses for those who purchase the full set. Sorry for the huge volume.
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
えーっと、まず一つ目が、えーっと、こちらなんですけど、ポストカード。
Um, the first one is this, the postcard.
あの、このポストカードはね、あのラバーマットのイラストを書いてくださったRosuuri先生のね、あの、ちょっと表情が、表情がちょっと…
This postcard features Rosuuri-sensei's illustration from the rubber mat, with a slightly different expression...
違うバージョンで、あの、なんと数量限定にはね...
With a different version, and for the limited edition...
団長、直筆でサインを書かせていただきます！
I will be hand-signing them myself!
あの、よろしくお願いします。
So, please look forward to it.
ちょっとね、数量限定なので、あの、ちょっと...
Since the quantity is limited, well...
頑張れ、頑張れ！ということで。
Good luck, everyone!
はい、えーっと、ちなみに通常版はね、箔押しの複製になっております。
Yes, and by the way, the standard edition features foil-stamped printed signatures.
そして特典二つ目なんですけど、
And for the second bonus,
こちらはね、ASMRボイスで、あの、4周年ありがとうボイスになってます。
this one is an ASMR voice, a "4th Anniversary Thank You" voice.
日頃の感謝を込めまして、団長思いを込めてね、録りましたので。
I recorded it with all my heart to express my daily gratitude.
ぜひ聴いてください！
So please give it a listen!
はい、この配信のあとにね、カートオープンするので、
Yes, the shop will open after this stream,
ぜひゲットしてください！よろしくお願いします。
so please go get them! Thank you very much.
そしてね、このあとメン限を22時15分からやるんですが、
And after this, I'll be doing a members-only stream starting at 22:15,
なんと今回、3Dで...ちょっと噛んじゃった。
and this time, it's a 3D... Oops, I stumbled over my words.
3Dでカラオケなので！
It's a 3D karaoke stream!
はい、ぜひぜひわちゃわちゃ楽しみにしててください。
So please look forward to the fun times!
それではちょっと長くなったんですが、
Now, I've talked for quite a while,
最後に、団員さん、そして今いるね、ホロメン、リスナーさんに、
but finally, to the Knights, the Hololive members, and the listeners here,
思いを込めて歌いますので。
I will sing with all my feelings.
最後の曲、いってみよう！
Let's go to the final song!
愛言葉IV
Ai Kotoba IV
想像なんてしてなかった現状
The current situation I never even imagined
君もそう思った？
Did you think so too?
最高値止まらないように
So that my peak doesn't stop
更新したい
I want to keep breaking my record
叶えたい夢まであとどれくらい
How much longer until the dream I want to fulfill?
誰も行ったことがない場所へ
To a place where no one has ever been
辿り着くまでは僕ら止まれない
Until we reach it, we can't stop
タブーしんどいけどどうかよろしくね
It's tough, but please stay with me
ねえねえ、たまにめでて
Hey, hey, love me sometimes
僕らだけじゃ作れないもの
Something we can't create on our own
僕とか君とか私とか
Me, and you, and myself
恋とか愛とかまとめて全部
Romance, and love, all together
君を置いてどこかに行っちゃうとか
Leaving you behind and going somewhere else
あり得ないよ
That's impossible
君がくれた音に弾けた火花に
In the sound you gave me and the sparks that flew
「はじめまして」からずっと恋しちゃってるんだよ
I've been in love with you ever since we first met
君のいない未来考えらんないよ
I can't imagine a future without you
これから先も二人がいいじゃん
Wouldn't it be great for the two of us to stay together?
意地になること逃げたくなった日もあったよ
There were days I was stubborn and wanted to run away
散々な僕のこと呼んでくれてありがとう
Thank you for calling out to someone as mess as me
君のいない未来考えらんないよ
I can't imagine a future without you
これから先も二人でそれから...
From now on, the two of us together, and then...
いいじゃん
It'll be great
妄想膨らんでいくストーリー
A story where delusions keep growing
完勝やけにへこんじゃって大丈夫
A complete victory, I was feeling quite down, but I'm okay
求めすぎはやだよ
I don't want to ask for too much
終わんない愛の連盟でしょう
It's an endless alliance of love, right?
ねえねえ、置いて愛でて
Hey, hey, keep me and love me
僕が君にできること
What I can do for you
まだまだまだまだあるけど
There's still so, so much more
驚かせたいから内緒なんだ
But it's a secret because I want to surprise you
君の愛がいつも勝っちゃうこと
That your love always wins
許さないよ
I won't allow that
君以外はやだわ
I don't want anyone but you
わがままはただ
My selfishness is just...
変わらないときめきを絶叫しちゃうのは
Screaming out this unchanging excitement
バカ
I'm a fool
君がくれた音に弾けた火花に
In the sound you gave me and the sparks that flew
「はじめまして」からずっと恋しちゃってるんだよ
I've been in love with you ever since we first met
君のいない未来考えらんないよ
I can't imagine a future without you
これから先も二人がいいじゃん
Wouldn't it be great for the two of us to stay together?
意地になること逃げたくなった日もあったよ
There were days I was stubborn and wanted to run away
散々な僕のこと呼んでくれてありがとう
Thank you for calling out to someone as mess as me
君のいない未来考えらんないよ
I can't imagine a future without you
これから先も二人でそれから...
From now on, the two of us together, and then...
いいじゃん
It'll be great
ドキドキしたいじゃんか誰だって
Everyone wants their heart to race, right?
安堵と後悔おかしくなっちゃった
Relief and regret, I've gone a bit crazy
痛みのないキスが花火
A painless kiss is like fireworks
僕らヴァンパイア
We are vampires
愛を吸っちゃっていいよ
You can go ahead and suck all my love
もう無理もう無理だって言うまで
Until you say, "I can't take any more"
こんな歌だったんだって
This is the kind of song it was
君が輝けるように
So that you can shine
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
出演：白銀ノエル、白上フブキ、百鬼あやめ、大空スバル
Cast: Shirogane Noel, Shirakami Fubuki, Nakiri Ayame, Oozora Subaru
猫又おかゆ、戌神ころね、宝鐘マリン、天音かなた、雪花ラミィ、風真いろは
Nekomata Okayu, Inugami Korone, Houshou Marine, Amane Kanata, Yukihana Lamy, Kazama Iroha
愛情は 聡明に
Love is wise
傷痕は いとをかし
Scars are very charming
もう体 堕痛いのだって 分かんなくなる
I don't even know that my body is hurting anymore
願い叶えてよ ギュッと抱きしめて
Grant my wish, hold me tight
遠い星へ ずっと連れてって
Take me away to a distant star forever
4周年ありがとうございます！！
Thank you so much for the 4th anniversary!!
今日のLIVEは楽しんでもらえたでしょうか...!?
Did you enjoy today's LIVE...!?
5年目も団員らしく遊んでくれ！
In our 5th year, keep playing like knights!
団員さんも一緒についてきてくれると嬉しいですッ♡
I'd be happy if you all continue to follow me ♡
大好きだおぉぉー！！
I love you all so much!!